

Contact

- mbfacu027@gmail.com
- +54 9 3541-226208
- 🡤 🛮 Route 28, Perú s/n, Tanti

Education

Elementary School 2012 - 2018

High School Technical Electronics

2018 - Present

Skills

- · Repair engines
- Learn quickly
- Multi tasking

Language

English (B1)

Main lenguaje Is Spanish

Facundo Moreno Blanco

Technician Electronics

About Me

Member of the secondary school science club for 2 years, experience in robotics for 3 years. Aspiring to study cybersecurity, skills for working with internal combustion engines, electrical installations or repairs, and learn new concepts quickly.

Work Experience

DEC 2024 - present

Mechanic

 I perform maintenance and repairs of combustion machines (stationary engines or gardening machines, etc.) of all types, including electrical ones.

DEC 2023- JAN 2024

Chef

- I was a cook, I made dishes that can be found in a restaurant bar, among the
- activities I did there were:
- Cooking
- · Washing dishes

JAN 2022- DEC 2023

Mowing the lawn

 I have cut grass on large, medium, and small plots of land, as well as weeded and pruned them.

Hobbies

- Motocross
- ·Offroad travel
- ·Music
- ·Motor sport
- Watch motogp races